(Howard:)Where's this coming from?
(Howard:)A few hours ago,
we both loved this song.
(Raj:)I still love it.
(Raj:)I just think there's
room for improvement.
(Howard:)You played it for Emily,
didn't you?
(Raj:)Yeah, so what?
You are such a wimp.
(Howard:)She didn't like it,
now you don't like it.
(Raj:)No, no. I'm just evolving
as a musician.
(Raj:)You're the one who's stuck
in the past.
The past was lunch!
(Leonard:)You know
what's really happening here?
(Howard:)Your girlfriend
is breaking up our band.
(Raj:)She has nothing to do with this.
(Raj:)I am my own man.
(Howard:)Oh, please. Your brain belongs
(Howard:)to whoever's willing
to sleep with you.
(Raj:)That is so not true.
Really?
(Howard:)Remember when you were gonna
get circumcised
(Howard:)for Rachel Bernstein?
(Raj:)That had nothing to do
with Rachel.
(Raj:)It was an overreaction
to a bad zipper injury.
(Howard:)I don't need this.
I'm quitting the band!
Fine, I quit, too!
Then get out of my house!
With pleasure!